filehungry.com 2012-06-21

# Privacy Statement - FileHungry Software Downloads

Privacy Statement  
  
Your privacy is important to us. The following notes provide a detailed explanation of the Privacy Policy and the privacy practices of the filehungry.com web site.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
You can visit the filehungry.com Web site without revealing any personal, identifiable information. The only information collected during a normal visit is your IP address, browser version, type of computer operating system, referring URL (if any) and a record of the content you viewed, along with the date and time of those requests. During normal browsing we do not collect or store information such as your name, mailing address or email address. This information gathered during this usage may be used to generate reports that measure site usage activity. This information is used to improve the site experience and monitor the activity on our servers. We may also share this information with advertisers and affiliates for information purposes.

 **IP Addresses**  
During your visit to filehungry.com we will record your activity by collecting and storing your IP address along with the requests for content from our servers for the purposes of statistics reporting, system administration, and security. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are on the Internet. Servers use the assigned IP address to identify your computer.

**Website Usage Tracking**  
As with most standard Web servers, filehungry.com Web server tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. In addition, we may use third party tracker to collect more traffic information. The information tracked includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, MIME type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, platform type, date and time stamp, and number of clicks. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information, and filehungry.com does not correlate this information with data about individual users. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers’ needs, analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We use Google Adsense and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. You may decline to accept cookies sent by the Site by selecting an option on your browser to reject cookies. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

**Linked Sites**  
filehungry.com contains links to other Web sites. Please be aware that our privacy policy does not apply to these linked sites.  
Third party sites linked to and from the Site are not necessarily under our control. We shall have no responsibilities or liabilities whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any such linked site or any link or linking program at any time. We do not necessarily endorse companies (or related products or services) to or from which the Site is linked. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to the Site, you do so entirely at your own risk. 

**Information Accuracy**  
Every effort is taken to insure the accuracy of the information presented on this web site, but filehungry.com the owner(s), webmaster(s), author(s) and affiliate(s) do not accept responsibility for the accuracy, completeness or authenticity of any of the information contained herein on this web site. This web site and the information presented is provided "as is" without any warranties or guarantees of any kind.

**Limitations of Liability**  
We reserves the right to modify the terms of this policy at any time and in our sole discretion, by posting a change notice to this page. Your continued use of this Web Site following our posting of a change notice will constitute binding acceptance of those changes.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.
